impartus.com 2019-08-28

# Impartus - Leading Video Platform for Education and Corporate

We work hard to earn and keep your trust. To safeguard your privacy we follow these core principles:

  * We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes.
  * We will never share your contact information with any other user without your consent. We will share this information only with the users who become your contacts.
  * Any sensitive information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technology.

Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use the Impartus service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our application, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.

Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the following:

  * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by Impartus.
  * How your personal information is used.
  * Circumstances that may lead to the sharing of personal information.
  * How to access and change your account information.
  * Security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected by Impartus. How you may contact Impartus.

Registration

In order to become an Impartus user, your school administrator or another designated person must first create an account on the web-based platform. To create an account you are required to provide general contact information like name, email address, and choose a password.

Profile Information:

We collect your personal details to maintain your user account on Impartus. Your profile includes general details like your address information, contact phone numbers, and alternate email address. These particulars help us maintain your up-to-date contact information on our records and to serve you better.

Children:

Children can only use our services under the supervision of their parents/legal guardians and we always suggest that minors (under the age of 13) not submit any personal information to us or use the service.

Information Use:

Impartus is a platform dedicated to making learning better through video. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on this application is used to help you describe yourself to other users. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual is collected by Impartus from the application (e.g., patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by Impartus. This information may be utilized by Impartus in such a manner as Impartus, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate.

Impartus Communications:

Impartus may communicate with you through email and notices posted on the Impartus application. This may include welcome emails that inform new users about various features of the service. Impartus may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, please send a request to [support@impartus.com](mailto:support@impartus.com?Subject=Support).

Sharing Information With Third Parties:

Impartus takes the privacy of its users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third party or parties for marketing purposes.  
We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our users by role (i.e. students, professors), subject, geographic location, or by company. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or products based upon aggregated data about our users’ activities on the application, please email Impartus’ customer service.

Partnering with Other Organizations to Offer Combined Services:

Impartus may partner with other online services to give you the combined results of both services. When we offer such combined services, it will always be your choice to make use of the combined services or not. In these cases, your personally identifiable information will only be passed from Impartus to our partner if you choose to use the combined service.

Legal Disclaimer:

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

Security:

All private information, such your address, can be accessed only by providing your password.

Changes to this Privacy Policy:

Impartus may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we process your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this application. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

Questions or Comments:

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please contact us at [support@impartus.com](mailto:support@impartus.com?Subject=Support).

Impartus Innovations

884, 6th and 7th Main, 22nd Cross, Sector-7,  
HSR Layout, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560102,   
India

+91 80 4662 0600
